As we all travel across the sea?
Raising our voices we take!
In the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go!
Everybody rejoices!
Now let's go get the sails all unfurled!
Here we are in between
the sea and the sky!
Ready now for adventure!
We're itching to try!
Get ready to roam!
So all aboard now we're set to go!
Set sail to the ocean so deep!
Ready for a truly grand adventure!
Well don't you think
that sounds really fun!
All this excitement is second to none!
As we all travel across the sea!
Raising our voices we take!
In the beautiful blue world!
Our spirits ready to go!
Everybody rejoices!
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled!
If there's something that
I just won't ever forget!
It's the way that I felt
when our journey was set!
Now I won't be scared!
As long as I keep that feeling there!
With that, let us keep up the pace!
While enjoying every
trip from place to place!
Our timid hearts get the rhythm ingrained!
So let's keep going, adventure awaits!
So many treasures await!
So now let's raise our voices in pride!
Laughing out when they are found!
With all the riches in
hand, everybody rejoices!
Party on, cause we stand tall and proud!
Life is adventurous, be
aware it's dangerous!
Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
Okay, you're flying.
That's not what I expected.
You're awful brave all of a sudden.
I had you running scared a minute ago.
Where did all this confidence come from?
I just got a little nervous
back there and I panicked.
I never dreamt that there
could be a person so
inherently negative that
they'd be immune to my ghosts?
And there's only one thing I
have to say to such a person!
Cheer up, life is good.
Ah, shut up!
You really think that you're safe for me
just because you can fly, little girl?
You're dealing with a sniper, flying or
dancing, and it makes no difference to me.
Allow me to explain.
This is my new weapon, Kabuto.
It features five pivots for
enhanced stability and reach.
And the breath dial I got from Sky Island
Activates the precise
moment that I take my shot,
Allowing me to spin the ammo
in any direction I desire.
so there's no escaping
this super slingshot!
Flame, flash, impact!
I've got every dial I need, and each one
makes my shot stronger than the last!
You're as good as gone once
I've got you in my sights!
Now prepare yourself for...
Hey, wait! She's gone already? What the
hell? What happened? Where did she go?
Right behind you.
Go on, try to hit me.
I've made it easy for you.
What the hell kind of monster are you?
No matter.
Here goes Butterfly Meteor!
What?
She's back to her normal size?
Why, you? Fine.
Try and fly away from this.
Mantis Meteora.
your hands you stabbed
them right through my chest
they're inside me it hurts
so much i can't even Feel it!
I'm gonna bleed to death! Stop! Don't!
That's it!
I'm a dead man!
I'm done for!
Idiot, look a little closer.
My hands are inside you, but
your skin's not even punctured.
You aren't hurt at all.
Let me reassure you that you
are still on the verge of death.
Do you feel it?
I'm mere inches away from wrapping
my fingers around your heart.
And squeezing it until it pops.
I'm begging you.
Please don't make my heart pop.
I don't want to die.
But you are going to die.
Now.
Writhe in beautiful agony.
And die.
Please stop.
Don't do it. Please.
No I don't want it.
Yeah I can't actually do any of that.
You weren't bluffing.
You made me hurt my hand.
Come on. Just. Think about it.
If I could actually crush
your heart like that,
you'd have been dead the moment I
stuck my hands inside your chest.
It's still gotta be bad for my heart.
My hands didn't even
really touch your chest.
They just passed right through.
Even though
my body might
look just as solid as yours.
I can pass through anything
you can think of. As if.
There was nothing there.
Special attack Viper Star 6!
You weren't listening to me, were you?
Please, oh, this is just gross!
If I can pass through anything, what
makes you think your attacks will hit me?
Get back!
Get away from me!
Go away, damn you!
Leave me alone, you're freaking me out!
What's your plan now?
You can't harm me with any
of your feeble attacks!
Shut up!
If you were only bluffing earlier
when you threatened to crush my heart
and you were then that means as big
as you talk you can't even touch me!
I might not be able to attack you
But, you can't attack me either.
Isn't that right?
Mihawk.
What are you gonna do with those?
And Ghostwrap.
That's so quick.
Get off me, go away.
Ghostwrap.
I still attack!
Firebird star!
Damn it!
This is so not fair!
None of my attacks can touch her, but she
can hurt me with the snap of her fingers!
I'm not sticking around for this!
Get out of the way!
I can't see with you there!
Move it!
Move!
And ghost rap.
It's just one embarrassment after another.
I'm pathetic.
That's what I get for
thinking I had the upper hand
The bear?
I'd be careful.
Kumasi is much stronger than
the average bear, you know
This is impossible.
No one in our crew stands a chance against
this girl So why did I think I would?
And why'd I have to go bragging
that only I can take her down?
No matter how strong you are, you
don't stand a chance against her.
All you can do is run.
But don't worry, I'll
take care of her for you.
I thought this was my moment to shine.
And then of course, this happens.
I can't do this.
I just can't.
There's no way I can win.
I'm a gunner for sure.
And then that girl's gonna
capture everyone else!
And completely wipe out our crew.
I thought I could save them for once.
And now I need saving.
Please help me?
Save me!
Sniper King.
Tell me, Sniper King,
what would you do here?
Kumasi!
Bastard!
How dare you harm my sweet Kumasi?
And what the hell's with
that stupid mask you got on?
You're looking at the face of your doom.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I am the one and only Sniper King.
You're the exact same guy.
You're just wearing a dumb mask.
Gotta go!
You're just gonna run away.
Calm down.
You have to fight Usopp.
Shut up.
I've given all I've got.
There's no way I can win against her.
You know that's not true.
I know you're the kind
of man who can win this.
What history are you basing that on?
None that is terrible
motivation regardless think
carefully don't you find
her behavior a little odd?
Yeah that's been bugging me especially
how she got so confident all of a sudden
she was completely terrified of me and
running for her life back there if she
was impervious to my attacks all along
there was no point in running for me
like that she could have just flown away
or walk right through one of the walls.
But she didn't.
All she did was run away
screaming at the top of her lungs.
What was she freaking out
about if I couldn't hit her?
That's it!
Ruff! Ruff!
Gah!
Everything about her changed
the moment I lost sight of her.
So the question is, what happened?
I Got wrapped up in dealing
with that stupid zombie bear!
That's when it happened right
when I lost sight of her?
Well, I guess I better hand you
over to Moria now. That's it.
I've got it
Look carefully.
There's gotta be someplace
to hide around here!
Like a trap door or hidden room.
I've got you.
I'm on to your tricks.
What?
Are those your last words?
Wait, stop!
What do you think you're aiming at?
That!
No, hang on!
Special attack Atlas Comet!
Just as I expected.
There it is.
I found your real body, ghost girl.
I can see you playing a stick.
But you can fly.
You can walk straight
through walls and people.
And to top it off.
You can change your size at will.
I'm no paranormal expert.
But it sure sounds like
you're a ghost to me.
So the question is: why would a
ghost run away from me? Like you did.
Leave me alone.
The only thing that makes sense is
that you had a physical body when.
I was chasing you.
What's your point?
My point is: you're a ghost duplicate.
You slipped out of your
body and became a ghost.
As soon as I lost sight of you.
That right there.
That's your real body.
I'm done falling for your tricks.
And here I thought you were
just some pessimistic idiot.
Did your little superhero
mass make you feel better?
Still.
I'm surprised you had the
wits to figure it all out.
But you're only about 90. Right?
I'm not just a ghost duplicate
being controlled by my real body.
My entire spirit is able
to detach and float free.
A hollow with its own will,
leaving my body empty.
Thanks for explaining.
I'm just curious.
What do you think would happen if
you didn't have a body to go back to?
Because I've got a feeling that my attacks
are actually going to
hit this time around.
You bastard.
Don't you dare!
I'll blow you to bits.
Here comes my big bang star.
That was way too close.
But you missed.
And it looks like it was a dud anyway.
This one won't be.
Like I'm giving you another shot.
Special hollow.
That one isn't going to
blow up, is it? Mini hollow.
A giant version of the ones from before.
Oh, this is messed up.
Get this thing off me, damn it.
You just stay put.
I'm not letting you lay
a finger on my real body.
Hey, come on, wait,
can't we talk about this?
Those little ones are turning up already.
Can't you just use those on me again?
This big one will blow me to pieces!
You can struggle all you want.
It won't help.
You're inside a ghost.
Ah!
Let me go!
Let me out of this damn thing!
Too bad you mucked up
that shot, Long Nose.
With a simple snap of my fingers, you'll
be reduced to a puddle of guts and goo.
No! Please don't! Please!
You won't stay that way for long.
Hogback will use whatever's left
of you to make a Long Nose zombie.
Kamikaze, wrap!
No! It vanished!
That was too close.
I used this impact dial
to absorb the explosion.
What are you...
Huh?
What the hell is this stuff?
It's a bluff. What do you mean?
You see, that shot I took at you earlier
landed exactly where I wanted it to.
And it wasn't a dud either.
It was actually a sticky star bullet.
I made sure you couldn't move after
you returned to your real body.
You did what?
Now that your ghost and body are one...
I can kill two birds with one shot.
Damn it.
You're the one who purified
our Captain Kumasi, aren't you?
What perfect timing.
Now take the creep out,
Lieutenant Hippo gentlemen.
Get back.
Oh.
Wait, is he actually strong after all?
So much pain.
I feel like my arm's going to snap it too.
Lieutenant Hippo!
Special attack!
Shiny Black Star!
Cockroaches!
Also known as the Roach Star!
So disgusting!
Get them off of me!
Help me!
I can't get away!
They're getting in my clothes!
Please, I hate cockroaches!
Please, somebody kill Lucy!
I had a feeling cockroaches
would freak you out.
But if you want to know what
you really should be scared of?
You're looking at him.
You shouldn't have
underestimated me, princess.
I was known through the
entire stretch of East Blue.
As the strongest man who ever lived.
Ten tons?
How can you even fit that much
strength in that scrawny body of yours?
I don't even have a chance, I
can't move Please, please stop!
Please don't!
I'll die if you hit me with that!
And get these disgusting roaches off me!
Not the hammer, please!
Not the cockroaches, either!
Please! Please!
Please spare my life! I'm sorry!
I'm begging you, please!
I swear I won't lay a finger on
your crew if you let me live!
Please don't kill me!
Please!
Stop crying!
It's too late!
GOLDEN POUND!
That is one sad ghost princess.
Though she should be
ashamed of herself passing
out at the sight of some
toy roaches in a balloon.
Talk about a stupid move.
Nobody challenges Usopp in the art
of negativity and lying and wins!
You just stay put until sunrise!
You hear that?
It sounded like the
samurai said something.
I couldn't understand.
A better question.
What in the hell's going on here?
What's going on?
In short, it looks like the
battle between them's over.
I've seen many fights in my life,
but I assure you none of them
have been anything like this.
So you think you can take my black
blade Chess away from me, do you?
Oh, I'm taking it.
I'm about to cut you down and
wrench it from your cold, dead body.
Oh, I see.
Feeling cocky today, are we?
Whoa, easy.
It's not a good idea to provoke him.
It looks to me that you already
have three swords. True.
But one's broken.
And I've gotten used to carrying
three, so it feels weird not to.
See?
I use three-sword style.
Three-sword style, huh? Never heard of it.
Is it some sort of circus act?
No, it's nothing like that.
I assure you it's too
bad I wish I could show
you but I'll just beat
you with two swords.
Interesting.
I can sense you're very skilled
Feeling that I've long forgotten
is welling up inside me once more.
It's as if I'm facing some sort
of a beast a savage animal!
The strange sensation echoing deep in my
bones makes me feel as
if I'm dancing on air.
That's right there!
No bother to drive!
It's not a gun,
it's a thrust, one of my techniques,
but when I use it, it doesn't
do nearly as much damage.